mytinyphone.com 2019-06-03

# Free ringtones and free phone wallpapers.

This privacy policy describes how Mobe LLC ("Mobe" or "we" or "us") uses personal information in running our business. MyTinyPhone is available from our websites, including but not limited to, www.mytinyphone.com, m.mytinyphone.com ("Websites") and mobile application ("Mobile Apps"). We refer to our Website visitors and Mobile App users as users ("Users") of MyTinyPhone's Services ("MyTinyPhone"). Please read our Terms of Service and our online safety and best practices guidelines. By visiting any of the Websites or using any of the Mobile Apps, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in the Privacy Policy. 

**1\. What information we collect?**

When you use MyTinyPhone, we collect your browser information (which typically includes browser type, version, host operating system and browser language) and IP address. This information is gathered for all visitors. In general, you can browse this website without giving us any additional information. However, to enjoy the benefits of a number of the services offered on this website, we need to have certain information about you. To access these services, you will, from time to time, be asked to submit personal information about yourself. In order to provide you with an account at MyTinyPhone that allows you to store your preferences and which includes other benefits and conveniences of our service, we need to collect information from you when you register such as your screen name and password, gender, date of birth, email address, mobile phone information, location (by country) and local time zone. You will also be asked about your desire to receive a number of optional services that include newsletters, competitions, alerts, SMS text messages, live chats, message boards and other benefits of MyTinyPhone membership. 

Should you choose to include additional personal information to be displayed on your user profile on our website we will necessarily process these details. Voluntarily submitted profile details means we may also collect from you information such as: 

  * more detailed contact information (including hometown and/or a picture of yourself);
  * information regarding your personal or professional interests;
  * your likes and dislikes;
  * information regarding your experiences with our services

If you choose to submit information about your religious or philosophical beliefs, your health, sexual life, racial or ethnic background, criminal history or trade union membership MyTinyPhone would necessarily have to process those details in operating your account and profile and your submission of such information would be your explicit consent for us to do so.

If you make any postings to public areas, or by providing content, then this information will be stored on our databases for public viewing, and in such case any personally identifiable information you submit will be publicly available and can be read, collected and used by other users, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable MyTinyPhone and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy.

**2\. Information on visitors**

During the course of any visit to MyTinyPhone, the pages you see, along with something called a "cookie", is downloaded to your computer. Most websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to ascertain whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. Any information that is supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better service and assists us to analyze the profile of our visitors. Cookies make it easier for you to maintain your preferences on MyTinyPhone, and by seeing how you use MyTinyPhone; we can tailor our website around your preferences. For example: if on a previous visit you went to the mobile wallpaper section, then we might find this out from your cookie and highlight wallpapers that might interest you on your next visit.

**3\. More information about cookies**

The purpose of cookies used by MyTinyPhone has been previously explained above in this Privacy Policy. When you enter a site that utilizes "cookies" your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie, provided your internet browser is set to accept them (most are by default). Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to that user. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You can, should you chose, disable the cookies from your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. For example, if you are using Internet Explorer, this can be done by selecting "Tools / Internet Options" and then reviewing your privacy settings or selecting "delete cookies". This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the services that this website has to offer.

**4\. Use and storage of your personal information**

When you supply any personal information to MyTinyPhone (e.g., for competitions, MyTinyPhone Community services or MyTinyPhone membership) we may have legal obligations towards you based upon privacy laws and regulations in the way we deal with that data. We will collect the information fairly, that is, we will explain how we will use it and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else.

The information you provide to MyTinyPhone will be used for the following reasons: 

  * to ensure that content from our site is presented to you in the most effective manner and to personalize your visit to our site;
  * to enable us to continuously enhance the MyTinyPhone service, to serve advertising, and to provide to you information, products or services which we feel may be of interest to you (which also helps keep our service free);
  * to occasionally carry out market research including internal analytical research which will enable us to constantly improve your experience on MyTinyPhone;
  * to carry out our obligations arising from any agreements that may have been entered into between you and us;
  * to allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;
  * to notify you about changes to or other information about our service

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service(s) you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of you no longer wish to continue your status as a MyTinyPhone member. In some circumstances it may be necessary to retain your personal information to deal with any disputes. Accordingly, MyTinyPhone may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of MyTinyPhone Community services for a period necessary to fulfill such purpose. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other MyTinyPhone services (e.g. competitions), that information will be held only as long as necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

Your personal data will be stored on our backup system, which is kept in case of loss of data. It may be that where data is lost, the personal data held on you as part of our backup system is used to restore your account to its status before the loss of data. All personal data (including communication data) stored on the backup system shall be held in accordance with the Data Retention Directive.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access. MyTinyPhone may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for. For example, we may wish to provide you with password reminders or notify you that a particular service has been improved or suspended. The only way you can opt out of receiving these types of administration communications would be to close your registration.

**5\. Disclosure of your information**

We will not pass on your personal information to third parties except in accordance with (i) this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, (ii) where there is a proposed sale or restructuring of Mobe LLC or (iii) where we are required by law to disclose that information. We do not share, sell, rent or trade personally identifiable information with third parties for their promotional purposes. Your personally identifiable information will never be supplied to anyone outside MyTinyPhone without first obtaining your consent, except where we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it without obtaining your consent in advance, or where there is a proposed or consummated sale or restructuring of Mobe LLC. Accordingly, we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the MyTinyPhone service or using the MyTinyPhone name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. We employ service providers and other companies and individuals to perform functions and provide services on our behalf who may have access to your member information needed to perform their functions and also to provide you with the services that you have requested, but may not use it for any other purpose. Such service providers may include credit card transaction processors, communication platform providers, and hosting services providers, and the information that could be provided to these service providers may include names, credit card numbers, email addresses and mobile phone numbers. Such service providers will be subject to appropriate contractual arrangements and security obligations as required by law. MyTinyPhone may also provide aggregate (but not personally identifiable) statistics about our members, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors. MyTinyPhone does contain third party advertising and sponsorship. These third-party websites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our website directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads, to personalize advertising content, to compile anonymous statistics and otherwise monitor the effectiveness of their campaigns. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites are not covered by this policy.

**6\. Direct Marketing**

We would like to provide you with information via email about new products, promotions, special offers and other information which we think you may find interesting. We fully appreciate that "spam" has become a problem in recent years and this is why we make sure you have the power to choose whether or not you want to receive such mailings. We will give you the option of opting in to receive any such marketing mailings when you register for MyTinyPhone, or afterwards via an email message or web page screen. If you choose to opt in, you may at any time afterwards change this preference.

**7\. Links to other websites**

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

**8\. Children**

We do not knowingly collect or store personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 unless or except as permitted by law. If we are made aware that we have received personally identifiable information from someone under 13, MyTinyPhone will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records.

**9\. Ownership Changes**

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the MyTinyPhone business, or individual business units owned by Mobe LLC, were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the provisions of the current privacy policy.

**10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy page, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently, and at least each time you submit personal information to MyTinyPhone. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage. The date of the most recent revisions will also appear on this page. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
